[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
SURMA: With the upcoming Edge 16,
SURMA：随着Edge 16的到来，
all major browsers have full support for CSS Grid.
所有主要的浏览器都完全支持CSS Grid。
In its most basic form, it's like Flexbox in two dimensions
在最基本的形式上，它就像二维的Flexbox
instead of one.
而不是一个。
But Grid packs a lot more capabilities
但是Grid包含了更多功能
and will probably become one of the core tools every web
并可能会成为每个网站的核心工具之一
developer should know.
开发人员应该知道。
CSS Grid allows you to lay out your elements
CSS Grid允许您布置元素
in a grid, similar to tables, but without the annoying table
在网格中，类似于表格，但没有烦人的表格
markup and all the weird special cases around tables.
标记以及表格周围所有奇怪的特殊情况。
And it's inherently responsive too.
而且它本身也具有响应能力。
Grid is very powerful, too powerful to cover everything
网格非常强大，无法覆盖所有内容
in a micro tip.
在一个小技巧。
But in its most basic form, you start with display grid.
但是从最基本的形式开始，您需要从显示网格开始。
You set up your grid by defining rows and columns
您可以通过定义行和列来设置网格
using grid template rows and grid template columns.
使用网格模板行和网格模板列。
In this example, I only used fixed width and the special fr
在此示例中，我仅使用固定宽度，而特殊的fr
unit that distributes free space.
分配可用空间的单位。
But Grid offers many tools to make the layout even more
但是Grid提供了许多工具来使布局更加合理
flexible.
灵活。
Once the grid is defined, the children of the grid container
定义网格后，网格容器的子代
will be laid out to occupy exactly one cell.
将被布置为恰好占据一个单元。
If that's not what you want, you can
如果那不是您想要的，您可以
assign areas that can span multiple rows
分配可以跨越多行的区域
and columns to some elements.
和一些元素的列。
The elements you don't place manually
您不需要手动放置的元素
will be placed in the available cells.
将放置在可用单元格中。
Isn't that handy?
那不方便吗？
If you want to know more about Grid, how
如果您想进一步了解Grid，如何
to do responsive designs, and what else you can do,
做响应式设计，还有您可以做些什么，
take a look at Rachel Andrew's gridbyexample.com.
看看Rachel Andrew的gridbyexample.com。
And that's great for you.
这对您来说很棒。
It's like the web of the '90s done right, kind of.
就像90年代的网络做得正确一样。
I don't know, whatever.
我不知道，随便
See you next time.
下次见。
This is a subscribe button.
这是一个订阅按钮。
And this is more Supercharged.
而且这更加增压。
While you consider clicking those buttons,
当您考虑点击这些按钮时，
let me tell you a joke.
让我告诉你一个笑话。
So a man goes into a bar, and the bartender says,
一个男人走进酒吧，酒保说，
what can I get you?
我能给你什么？
And the man says, well, I would like a whiskey.
男人说，好吧，我想要威士忌。
And then-- no wait, it's the other way around.
然后-不用等待，反之亦然。